

Dorian-Ioan VELICI

• Home: Spl. 1 Decembrie 1918, bl. 29, ap. 16, 305500, Lugoj, Romania

Email: dorian.ioan_velici@hotmail.com Phone: (+40) 720390573

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/dorian-ioan-velici/

Gender: Male Date of birth: 15/12/1996 Place of birth: Lugoj, Romania Nationality: Romanian

ABOUT ME

I am a problem-solving person. Both in my personal & professional space, I particularly enjoy using my skills to solve challenging problems, to future improve processes and to prevent less desired outcomes from occurring.

By working at FORVIA Hella Lugoj as a Technical Assistant in the Backend Area, I gained on-field demonstrated experience, developed my general knowledge and analytical skills around PCBtesting equipment, CNC routing machines & automatic soldering stations by configuring / maintaining the equipment, optimizing / redesigning the programs and, finally - improving the overall manufacturing processes when needed.

As a sideline activity I configure, upgrade & optimize Windows OS-based systems & work on improving the overall performance, gaining stability and fix problems caused by software-related issues.

As a sideline activity I also enjoy developing (both programming & designing) websites. This hobby helped me gain good knowledge around HTML, Cascading Style Sheets markup languages and JavaScript programming language.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

[01/10/2017 - 01/07/2021]

Information Technology Engineer Degree

"Ioan Slavici" University - Faculty of Engineering

City: Timişoara | **Country:** Romania |

WORK EXPERIENCE

[11/10/2024 - Current] Website Developer

City: Lugoj | Country: Romania

Link: https://dorian-ioan-velici.github.io/personal-website/

Website development - both programming & designing web pages as a sideline activity.

[27/04/2023 – Current]

Technical Assistant (Backend Area)

FORVIA Hella https://www.hella.com/hella-ro/

City: Lugoj | Country: Romania | Email address: dorianioan.velici@forvia.com | Name of unit or department: PCB Production (Backend Area) | Business or sector: Manufacturing

My usual tasks consist in:

- regular analytical & problem-solving activities;
- technical maintenance and equipment repair;
- program optimization / redesign for many essential devices used at PCB-manufacturing processes.

The equipment I'm most familiar with:

- ICT/EOL teststands (Aeroflex 4250 & National Instruments NI LabVIEW), Takaya Flying Probe
- automatic selective soldering machines (SEHO SelectLine C systems);
- CNC routing machines used in the PCB depaneling process (Schunk & Asys Divisio 2000 Ergo millings);
- Maestro 4S cutting stations;

- plus other PCB-manufacturing factory equipment.

[02/06/2015 - Current] **IT Technician**

City: Lugoj | Country: Romania

As a sideline activity I also:

- Configure, upgrade & optimize Windows OS-based systems;
- Troubleshoot & fix hardware failures;
- Improve the overall performance, gain stability & fix problems caused by software-related issues.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Romanian

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING C1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DRIVING LICENCE

Motorbikes: AM В Cars:

SKILLS

NI LabVIEW | Computer Literacy | PCB Debugging | Process Optimization | CNC Programming | Process Failure Mode Effects Analysis | Website Development